

OLAKUNLE IBRAHIM

• DETAILS •

Sweden 0736565835 klexy2402@gmail.com

> Driving license B

• SKILLS •

Communication Skills

Good Team Player

Flexibility and Adaptability

Data Analysis Skills (Analytics Tools: Power BI, Qlik, Excel))

Data Engineering Skills (BigQuery, Tensorflow, GCP)

Programming Skills (Java, C#, JavaScript, Python)

Development Framework (HTML, CSS, React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, Android Studio)

Database Skills (MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB)

Cloud Computing (Google Cloud, MS Azure)

UI/UX Skills

Digital Marketing

• HOBBIES •

Travelling, Football, Chess game, Gym

• LANGUAGES •

English

Swedish

• LINKS •

Web portfolio

PROFILE

Experienced in design, Implementation, testing, installation, and maintenance of software systems. Proficient in different development platforms, programming languages, data engineering and analytic, and information system management. Experienced with the latest development tools, technologies, and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cashier/ Restaurant Assistant at Hubertus Restaurant, Stockholm

August 2015 — December 2016

- Worked productively with Restaurant Team to provide better customer service experience.
- Effectively service delivery under pressure.
- Worked to ensure customer satisfaction at all time.

Local Assistant at EFMAB, Stockholm

January 2015 — July 2015

Cleaning and hall management

Special Assistant, Legislative Arm at Legislator, House of Representative, Abuja June 2009 — May 2012

- Cordinate youth empowerment and development programs.
- Special duties and social engagement.
- Successfully managed publicity and enlightment services.

Production Manager at Narconon Nigeria (NGO), Lagos

June 2007 — May 2012

- Worked to ensure plans execution and succesfulness.
- Developed strategies for events and productivity.
- Ensured widely spread campaign for achieving success and effectiveness.
- Partnership and corroborate UNODC concepts.

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Information System, Lund University, Lund

August 2020 — June 2021

Bachelor of Science in Software Development, Kristianstad University, Kristianstad

August 2017 — June 2020

Diploma in Computer Science, Kwara State Polytechnic, Ilorin

September 2001 — December 2003

CERTIFICATION

Data Engineering with Google Cloud - (In progress), Coursera.org

March 2021

Digital Marketing Certificate, Google Fundamental Digital Marketing 2019 - 2019

Y EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Group Work at Course Projects Development, Kristianstad University, Kristianstad 2017-2020

Application development.

Assistant Field Communicator/ Reporter at BBC, Lagos

2009 - 2010

Radio 5 Lagos.

Documentary about Nigeria Cultures and Traditions

Lead Field Communicator at UK DragonFly TV, Lagos

2010 - 2010

Project: Lagos Documentary

¶ REFERENCES

References available upon request